A Guide to the Paul B. Barringer Papers 1913-1919
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- Paul B. Barringer
  - Administrative Files 1906-1913
    - Smithfield 1906-1911 (Box-folder 2-104)
      - Walnut trees
    - Southern Railway Scholarship 1912 (Box-folder 2-105)
    - State Entomologist, J. L. Phillips 1907-1910 (Box-folder 2-106)
    - Swanson, Claude A., Governor of Virginia 1907-1908 (Box-folder 2-107)
    - Taft, President Wm Howard 1909 (Box-folder 2-108)
    - Telephones 1908 (Box-folder 2-109)
    - Tyler, J. Hoge, Ex-Governor 1910 (Box-folder 2-110)
    - War Department 1906-1907 (Box-folder 2-111)
    - Water/Sewage Systems 1907-1910 (Box-folder 2-112)
    - Wilson, Woodrow 1911 (Box-folder 2-113)
    - YMCA 1909 (Box-folder 2-114)
      - Notable letterhead: Young Men's Christian Association, VPI
      - Statement YMCA indebtedness fund Nov. 18, 1906-March 31, 1909
    - Women 1908 (Box-folder 2-115)
      - Letter to J. Ernest Walker indicating inability to accommodate ladies
    - Vawter, Charles Erastus (Box-folder 2-116)
- Paul B. Barringer
  - Administrative Files 1900-1913
    - Hazing 1908 (Box-folder 3-117)
    - Inventories 1908-1911 (Box-folder 3-118)
    - Agricultural Board Development 1907-1911 (Box-folder 3-119)
    - Leases and Contracts (1) 1900-1913 (Box-folder 3-120)
    - Leases and Contracts (2) 1900-1913 (Box-folder 3-121)
      - Notable letterhead: Hartford Steam Boiler
      - Notable letterhead: Hotel Astor
      - C. M. Camper's water right [Camper Spring]
      - Notable letterhead: Hygeia Herd
    - Investigation-Reply from Wade 1910 (Box-folder 3-122)
    - Investigations 1910 (Box-folder 3-123)
    - Investigation-Letters to Alumni 1910 (Box-folder 3-124)
  - Oversized Materials
    - Architectural blueprints of Virginia Polytechnic Institute feeding barn [three sheets originally in folder 120] (Box-folder 3-125)